awaytravel.com 2003-12-09

# Azumano/Away Travel Privacy Policy

**It is Azumano/Away Travel's** policy that **personal information** , such as your name, postal and email address or telephone number, is **private and confidential**. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible _only_ by designated staff, and is used _only_ for the purposes for which you provide the information.

_ If_ you also indicate on our site that _you would like to receive information about travel and services_ , publications or membership, your personal information will be added to appropriate mailing lists.  If at any time you change your mind and would like to add or remove your name from our mailing list, or correct your personal information, please email us at [info@azumano.com](mailto:info@azumano.com)

** No Release of Information to Third Parties**  
Personal information **will not be released to third parties**   Azumano/Away Travel will not provide or sell personal information to third parties.

** No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information**  
Azumano/Away Travel will track information about the visits to our web site. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.
